Yordanos Beneberu

+251963197542 | yordi.beneberu@gmail.com | Addis Ababa, Addis Ababa

Summary

Full stack Developer with more than 2 year experience as a full time employee in all phases of the SDLC, including Analysis, Design, Development, Testing, Maintenance, and Documentation of Enterprise-level web and windows applications using Microsoft Technologies. Logical and result-driven full stack developer dedicated to building and optimizing user-focused websites and applications. Judicious and creative when crafting effective websites, apps and platforms to propel competitive advantage and revenue growth. Technical proficient and analytical problem solver with calm and focused demeanor. Conduct manual test and debugging client projects for better company client relationships

Experience

Exceed IT System | Addis Ababa, Addis Ababa Intern | 06/2018 - 09/2018

· Developed Online Auction System using C#

Tohey Technologies PLC | Addis Ababa, Addis Ababa Intern | 06/2019 - 09/2019

Developed Sales Management System for the company. Technologies used:- Asp.net core, MsSql, Angular js

Sinbona Technologies PLC | Addis Ababa, Addis Ababa Junior Full Stack Developer | 03/2020 - 03/2021

- Managed development milestones from initial steps through final delivery.
- Adjusted design parameters to boost performance and incorporate new features.
- Writing readable, maintainable, high performance and clean code based on the business requirement using MongoDb,
 Node Js, React Js, Git (using clean Architecture concept).
- · Projects:-
 - -Garage Management System
 - -Lemmaji System

Tohey Technologies PLC | Addis Ababa, Addis Ababa Full Stack Developer | 03/2021 - Present

- · Managed development milestones from initial steps through final delivery.
- Gathered and defined customer requirements to develop clear specifications for project plan.
- Adjusted design parameters to boost performance and incorporate new features.
- Writing readable, maintainable, high performance and clean code based on the business requirement using C#, .Net core, MsSql, Angular is, React Js, Git (using clean Architecture concept).
- participating on the development and testing of different micro services.
- · setting of environments for release of system.
- Projects:-
- HRMS(Human Resource Management System):- Contains employee self-service, Attendance Management, Payroll, Dashboard etc.
- POS System:- allows the processing and recording of transactions

Skills

Node Js, Angular Js, .Net Core, MongoDb, MsSql, MySql, React Js, Entity Framework, C#, JavaScript

Education